geeki.in 2014-07-03

# Privacy Policy - BandyoWeb.com

We, the members of [bandyoweb.com](http://bandyoweb.com/) consider the privacy of our users with higher importance. Please take a look at the privacy documents before leaving the site.

 **Log Files**

We do take a log of user information that includes user IP addresses, type of browser, demographic information, date stamp, exit pages etc to analyze traffic movement in or out the site. But we never share your personal information with third party sites. You will never receive unsolicited emails from if you use your email address in comments.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**

We use cookies to identify user preferences, entering keywords, entering pages, exit pages etc to identify visitor movements in the site. This eventually helps us to improve the quality of our site. We solemnly declare that we never misuse your personal information with third party sites.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google Adsense use DoubleClick cookes to server ads on tech2auto.in.
  * Google use DART cookies to identify user preferences based on that they serve relevant ads. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting this Google Privacy Ads page: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**Third Party Advertisers apart from Google**

We do place third party advertisements in our site apart from Google Adsense. Advertisers may store click pattern, visitors IP address and other details by using cookies, Web Beacons, JavaScript. We can’t control cookies used by third party advertisers of our site. You can disable cookies from your web browser’s settings.

 **References**

We do cite references from our content to the actual resource. We use images, videos from third party sites. In most occasions we leave the credit as is. Please feel free to let us know if you found anything that violates your privacy policy.

 **User Safety**

We publish content that is safe for all ages. Please feel free to let us know if you find anything objectionable.

 **Security**

We do use security measures to protect your personal information. We don’t allow misuse of your personal data under any circumstances.

 **Distribution of Our Content**

We don’t allow users to distribute our content with third party sites without informing us. Copying contents from our site strictly violates our privacy policy.
